Nikolas Bogucharsky

Software Developer

```
var contactInfo ={
  location : 'Atlanta',
  github : 'github.com/niktechnopro',
  linkedin : 'linkedin.com/in/niktechnopro',
  personal : 'niktechnopro.com',
  email : 'niktechnopro@gmail.com'
}
```

Profile

Cisco certified network professional turned Software Develper. My unique professional experience stems from years of providing highest customer satisfaction and leading my crew in quality.

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, jQuery, SASS, AJAX/JSON, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, Redux, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Python, AWS EC2, Git, GitHub, Apache

Work history

```
function Work(role, time) {
    this.role = role;
    this.time = time;
}
```

let digitalCrafts = new
Work("Teacher Assistant",
"January 2018 - March 2018");

let aTT = new Work("Sr Network
Technician", "February 2012 September 2019");

let mySatelliteCompany = new Work("Instructor, Lead Technician", "February 2008 -February 2012");

Featured projects

LocDoc | github.com/niktechnopro/LocDoc

- LocDoc is a powerful tool that enables the user to find a doctor based on location, insurance, and specialty.
- Built with Node.Js/Express, React.js/Redux, MySQL, Google Maps API, and BetterDoctor API.

Village | github.com/niktechnopro/village

- Village is a ChatBot that features ability to summarize individual feelings to help building emotional intelligence in adolescent children. Noted for the best ChatBot idea at Hack The Violence Hackaton 2017.
- Built with Node.js, Express, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery.

Focus! | github.com/niktechnopro/Focus

- Focus! is a productivity timer based on the Pomodoro technique for efficiency improvement. It features the ability to set work and rest intervals as well as entertainment based on jokes API for long breaks.
- Built with HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery and JSON API for random Chuck Norris jokes.

Education

DigitalCrafts, Software Engineering Course Atlanta, GA | September 2017 - January 2018

• 16 weeks intensive, full-time school for software engineering **Georgia Institute of Technology**

Atlanta, GA | August 2015 - December 2015

• Computer Networks course with focus on SDN

Riga Technical University

Riga, Lativa | September 1997 - June 2001

• BSEE - Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering

Professional development

- Certified in CCNA R&S, CCNA Security, Juniper JNCIA,
 CompTIA A+, Network+, and Security+
- AT&T training programs: ICND1, ICND2, Electricity, Electronics, and Digital Communications